university.com 2016-05-12

# Privacy Policy - University.comUniversity.com

Our Practices Regarding Privacy

Katch, LLC, through its University.com website (hereafter referred to as “University.com”) is committed to ensuring the privacy and security of each user that visits our website. Your privacy rights are important to us and University.com is committed to respecting your online privacy and making sure that any information you share with us by using our website is properly protected.

We have established this University.com Privacy Policy so you know the importance we place on your privacy and so you can understand how we collect and use information collected from you when you visit our website or submit any personally identifiable information to us. This policy describes our overall privacy practices regarding information we collect on our web sites and through other Internet mediums. Our policy does not apply to the practices of companies that we do not own or control.

## Website Data

When you visit our website, we collect information on the efficiency and working of our site. The types of information your browser or Internet session automatically sends us each time you visit one of our sites, which we automatically collect, includes:

  * Your browser, e.g., Internet Explorer, Netscape Navigator.
  * Your Internet domain, e.g., AOL, Netcom, Earthlink, etc.
  * You computer’s operating system, e.g., Windows, Macintosh, UNIX, Linux.
  * Your navigation path, i.e., the URLs of where you come to our site from, which of our pages you visit, and where you go as you leave.
  * Your IP address.

This information lets us see how users find our sites, and it tells us which pages users visit most frequently so we can make our Web sites more useful. We keep this information for an indefinite amount of time to improve the operation of our site and to provide better services to our users.

## Cookies

Our websites use cookies (small files containing program code that reside on your computer), to provide usage statistics about our web site, and to understand where visitors learn about our web site. We also may use cookies to simplify the re-entering of your data. You can adjust your browser settings to opt out of the use of cookies by having your browser disable cookies. Look for the cookie options in your browser in the Options or Preferences menu.

Additionally, we and our third party partners (e.g., third party ad networks or website analytics service providers) use cookies, web beacons, and other technologies to receive and store certain types of information whenever you interact with us through your computer or mobile device. This information, which may include the pages you visit on our or our partners’ sites, which web address you came from, the type of browser/device/hardware you are using, or an IP-based geographic location, helps us recognize you, customize your website experience and make marketing messages more relevant. These companies use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, hardware/software information) during your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. At this time, we do not respond to browser “do not track” signals, and we do not control third parties’ collection or use of your information or whether they respond to these signals. However, we, and these third parties, may provide you with ways to choose not to have your information collected or used in this way. To learn more about targeted ads or to opt-out of this type of advertising, visit the [Network Advertising Initiative website](http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices) or [Digital Advertising Alliance website](http://www.aboutads.info/).

## Contact Information

In addition to the data that your browser or Internet session sends us automatically, we may also collect personally identifiable information (your first and last name, telephone number, mailing address, email address, date of birth and other general information that may be requested by our advertising partners) if you enter it when using our website. This contact information is stored on our servers and used to fulfill your information request. If you have not opted out of its use, we may share it with our data licensees, including our advertising clients and their vendors, and other advertising partners.

## Opt-Out, Your Choices and Changing Information You Provided to Us

You may choose whether or not you receive communications from us as follows: You may also opt out or change or modify information you have previously provided to us by contacting us by doing any one of the following:

  * Marketing Email Opt-out: Each of our marketing email communications includes an opt-out link. You may click on that link and opt out from receiving marketing email.
  * Refusing Cookies: You can adjust your browser settings to opt out of the use of cookies by having your browser disable cookies. Look for the cookie options in your browser in the Options or Preferences menu.
  * Submit a “Stop contacting me” request on our Contact Us page.
  * Call us at (310) 219-6202
  * Send a letter to: University.com, 2381 Rosecrans Ave., Suite 400, El Segundo, CA 90245

## Contacting You

Different advertisers and advertising companies have different methods of following up with you on information requests. Some send brochures in the mail, others reply via email or some may contact you by telephone. By using our service to request information from our advertising clients and advertising partners, you are giving permission to University.com and these parties (or their partners and vendors) to contact you using the methods of their choice, notwithstanding your possible listing in the National Do-Not-Call Registry, now or in the future (unless and until you opt-out from receiving communications from us or such partners, as applicable). In addition to commercial messages, we may also contact you to help improve our operations, to introduce new services, to conduct surveys and similar research, or to ensure that our advertising clients have followed up with your information requests in a timely manner.

## Children’s Privacy

University.com is not directed at individuals less than sixteen years of age. We do not intend to collect personal information from such individuals.

## Questions or Comments

We invite you to contact us if you have questions or comments about our Privacy Policy or you want to change the personally identifiable information you have provided to us. You may contact us by:  
Sending a letter to: University.com, 2381 Rosecrans Ave., Suite 400, El Segundo, CA 90245  
Calling us at (310) 219-6202  
Emailing us at: [privacy@University.com](mailto:privacy@University.com)

If you are a California resident and would like to request certain information regarding the disclosure of your personal information to third parties for direct marketing purposes, please submit your request by writing us, calling us or emailing us using the contact information listed above.

## Privacy Policy Changes

University.com may change this Privacy Policy at any time. Should we revise this Privacy Policy in the future, we will immediately publish the amended Privacy Policy on our website. We recommend that you check our website frequently to view recent changes or updates.

## Definitions

The definitions for certain terms used in this Privacy Policy are listed below.

### COOKIES

Data created by a Web server that is stored on a user’s computer. It provides a way for the Web site to keep track of a user’s patterns and preferences and, with the cooperation of the Web browser, to store them on the user’s own hard disk. The cookies contain a range of URLs (Web addresses) for which they are valid. When the browser encounters those URLs again, it sends those specific cookies to the Web server. For example, if a user’s ID were stored as a cookie, it would save that person from typing in the same information all over again when accessing that service for the second and subsequent time during the same browser session. You can opt out of the use of cookies by having your browser disable cookies or warn you before accepting a cookie. Look for the cookie options in your browser in the Options or Preferences menu.

### IP (INTERNET PROTOCOL) ADDRESS

This is the address of a computer attached to a TCP/IP network. Every client and server station must have a unique IP address. Client workstations have either a permanent address or one that is dynamically assigned for each dial-up session. IP addresses are written as four sets of numbers separated by periods; for example, 211.472.58.9.

### BROWSER SESSION

A browser session is defined as the period of time a browser is in consecutive use. The session begins when you open the browser and ends when you close it. When you reopen the browser, you begin a new session.

### URL (UNIFORM RESOURCE LOCATOR)

This is an Internet address. URLs are used to locate sites on the Internet and to navigate between sites and pages within sites. The URL for University.com is www.university.com.

## Trademarks

This Privacy Policy contains certain trademarks. Windows and Internet Explorer are registered trademarks of Microsoft Corporation. Macintosh is a registered trademark of Apple Inc. All other trademarks are the property of their respective owners.
